zzinsider.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Trendzz

Effective as of May 19th, 2016 (the “Effective Date”)

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to the TRENDZZ Web Site (the “Site”). It does NOT apply to other online or offline websites, products or services of TRENDZZ or its affiliates.

This Policy explains what information we collect about you and what we do with it. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, and we will notify you of any material changes to the Policy by posting the new Policy here and changing the “Effective Date” at the top. We may also use alternative methods to alert you to changes to the Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. By using or navigating the Site or any portion of the Site, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to be bound by this Policy or any modified Policy as posted. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use or visit any the Site or any portion of the Site.

Information collected.

We only record e-mail addresses as for personal information. When you visit our Site, we collect certain anonymous demographic information about you, including your IP address, zip code and browser program. We also collect information regarding your use of the Site through the use of cookies (see below for more about cookies). If you choose to post messages, comments or other information in one on our Site, we will maintain on the Site such information about you as you choose to disclose in your posting.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We will maintain a record or notes of communications with you regarding your account.

How your information is used.

We use your information in order to fulfill your orders and/or requests, to facilitate your viewing of our Site, to communicate with you, and to provide you with information about the Site, some of our partners and third party companies in which we think you may be interested. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and Site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally.

TRENDZZ uses your e-mail address to contact you when necessary and to send periodic e-mail newsletters and promotional e-mails to you about services and products offered by us as well as by third party companies in which we think you may be interested. Users may opt out of this service by clicking on the “opt-out” link provided on the Site.

We use IP addresses and anonymous demographic information to tailor your experiences at our Site by showing content in which we think you will be interested and displaying content according to your preferences. Anonymous demographic information is shared with advertisers and market researchers on an aggregate basis. We use information collected to evaluate and improve our services. We may develop and use, in our sole discretion, consumer research, which may be based on your use of our services.

Information shared with third parties.

In some cases, we will share information we collect (including email addresses and/or anonymous demographic information) with third party companies who may offer products or services in which we believe you may be interested. We also share this information with third parties with whom we partner to co-promote and administer our Site.

We may also share information we collect with third party service providers to manage certain aspects of the services we provide, such as maintaining our servers and processing or fulfilling orders for products and services you purchase through the Site.

We may also disclose your information in special cases if required to do so by law, court order or governmental authority or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including, for instance, to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with the rights or property of TRENDZZ, another user or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

In the event of a change in ownership or a merger with, acquisition by, or sale of assets to, another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all user information collected in connection with the Sites, including but not limited to email addresses, to a separate entity. TRENDZZ will notify you (via a posting on the Site or the Policy or via email (in our discretion)) of such a transfer, and you may choose to modify your registration information at that time. This means that if you are concerned about your personal data migrating to a new owner, you can deactivate your account.

Information submitted in public forums.

The Site may offer chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or news groups to our users. Please remember that any information disclosed in these areas becomes public information. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in any public forum, and you do so at your own risk.

Use of Cookies.

Cookies are pieces of information generated by web servers and stored on your computer for future access. The Site uses cookie technology to enhance your online experience by making it easier for you to navigate through our Site or to make a feature work better. Generally, cookies can be disabled at your discretion. However, you must accept cookies in order to navigate the Site.

Security of Information.

TRENDZZ takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you and to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control.

Website Links.

The Site may contain links to other Internet sites, resources and sources of TRENDZZ. By clicking on any banner advertisement or other link, you will be redirected off the Site and to third party websites. TRENDZZ is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of such websites. You should make sure that you read and understand the privacy policies of these sites and direct any concerns regarding external links to the site administrator or webmaster of that third party website. TRENDZZ E-Mail.

All e-mails you receive from us will include specific instructions on how to unsubscribe, and you may unsubscribe at any time. Additionally, we give you the following options for removing your information from our database:

(1) Send an email to info@TRENDZZ.com (please indicate that you would like to be unsubscribed from TRENDZZ emails); you may correct or update the email address you have provided to TRENDZZ by sending us an email at info@TRENDZZ.com. TRENDZZ Support Team.

TRENDZZ recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of our Site or your dealings with TRENDZZ, please contact us at info@TRENDZZ.com.

From time to time, we may share your personal information, such as your email address with carefully screened companies that offer products or services that we believe you may enjoy. If you do not want us to share your email address with such third parties, please send us your request, to sinfo@TRENDZZ.com. Your opt out request will be processed within 30 days of the date it was received.
